# Ved Prakash

98106 86583 | vedp3141@gmail.com | <u>LinkedIn</u> | <u>Github</u>

#### Profile

An curios, determined and passionate final year student pursuing opportunites in **App Development**. Adept at handling multiple tasks on a daily basis **competently** and at working well under pressure. Have decent **experience** in **App** and **Web development** roles.

#### EDUCATION

# Netaji Subhas University of Technology (West Campus)

Delhi, India

Bachelor of Technology in Information technology

Aug. 2019 - May 2023

#### EXPERIENCE

# App Development Intern

March 2020 - June 2021

#### ATTEND IT

- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features
- Work with outside data sources and APIs
- Unit-test code for robustness, including edge cases, usability, and general reliability
- Work on bug fixing and improving application performance
- Discover, evaluate, and implement new technologies to maximize development efficiency

#### Full Stack Web Developer

July 2021 – Present

#### Repulse Technologies Private Limited

- Take ownership of the desktop app which may also involve having a decent amount of knowledge of DOM optimisations, Render time optimisations, and other performance optimisation techniques.
- Work with the backend team to integrate new features and solutions.
- Work with the product and RD team to understand business goals and help bring them to fruition
- Work with the product and RD team to understand business goals and help bring them to fruition

# Projects

## Mister Policy | Vuejs, Nuxtjs, Nodejs, AWS

- Frontend Development Using Vue. js and Nuxtjs is one of the most popularly used JS frameworks for developing UIs and single-page applications.
- Node.js is used for backend development because it offers high performance for real-time applications and Helps in building Cross-functional Teams.

## MDTEL Networks Management System Website | Html, Css, Bootstrap, Jquery, Php

- An internal management system for MDTEL Networks allows employees to view their allocated tasks.
- PHP and MYSQL used for backend development PHP is an open source scripting language that can be used to
  write websites and any kind of web-based application and service.

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages : C++, C, JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML/CSS, Nodejs, Php, MongoDB, MySQL, TypeScript, Ty

Frameworks: VueJS, NestJS, Flutter

Developer Tools: Git, Google Cloud Platform, VS Code, Postman, Docker, Heroku